1. انتبه، انتبه!
(watch out !)
2. أنصت، أنصت!
(listen!)
3. واجه خوفه.
(he faced his fear)
4. تشاجر الجيران.
( the neighbors argued)
5. تصالح مع عائلته.
(he made up with his family)
6. مسح الأرض.
he wiped the floor)
7. طبخ الطعام.
(he cooked the food)
8. احتفل بنجاحه.
(he celebrated his success)
9. ندم على سوء عمله.
(he regreted his wrong doing)
10. شمّ بأنفه.
(he smelled with his nose)
11. يلمس بيده.
(he touched with his hand)
12. قصّ شعره.
(he cut his hair)
13. ركّب القطع.
(he put together the pieces)
14. فصّل المحرك.
(he took apart the engine)
15. اتّبع المعجبون النجم.
(the fans followed the star)
16. نزع المعطف.
(he took off the coat)
17. استحمّ قبل النّوم.
((he took a shower before going to bed)
18. ضحك الجمهور.
(the audience laughed)
19. بكى الطفل.
(the kid cried)
20. حزن الوالدان.
(the parents got sad)
21. أمسك يدها.
(he held her hand)
22. رجع إلى الخلف.
(he went backward)
23. تجاهل التّحذير.
(he ignored the warning)
24. وقّع الوثيقة.
( he signed the document)
25. أوقع القلم.
(he droped the pen)